shodor.org 2011-06-21

# Shodor: Privacy

Privacy

At Shodor we are committed to protecting your privacy whenever we collect personal information. You can navigate throughout most of our site without giving us any self-identifiable information. Please read the complete Shodor.org (Shodor) privacy statement below. 

Collecting your Personal Information 

Shodor will notify you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you subscribe to an electronic mail newsletter, put input in a comment box, or visit a part of our site where a login is necessary. Personal information collected by Shodor is often limited to just electronic mail addresses. 

Use of Your Personal Information 

Shodor uses your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To deliver services that you request 
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you 
  * To keep you informed about newsletters, updated information, and workshops 
  * To measure the effectiveness of our site and programs 

Control of your Personal Information 

When you give us your personal information, Shodor will not share this information with third parties. It will only be used for the purposes illustrated in the "Use of Your Personal Information" section. If Shodor sends you an electronic message that contains hyperlinks, when viewing this information you may pass on self-identifiable data to our servers before you reach your final destination. 

Cookies and other technologies 

Shodor uses cookies only to maintain session information when users sign in to specific areas of the site, and when used these cookies are set to expire within a fixed period of time. 

Contact Shodor 

If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, you can contact us at: 

The Shodor Education Foundation, Inc.   
300 West Morgan Street, Suite 1150   
Durham, NC 27701   
Tel: (919) 530-1911   
Fax: (919) 530-1944   
Email: [webmaster@shodor.org](mailto:webmaster@shodor.org)
